<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>konqueror.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Konqueror</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKonquerorxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">瀏覽器_Konqueror</name>
  <summary>KDE File Manager &amp; Web Browser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El gestor de fitxers i navegador web del KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Správce souborů &amp; prohlížeč Webu pro prostředí KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">KDE sien Dateipleger un Nettkieker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KDE's bestandsbeheerder &amp; webbrowser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka plików i sieci dla KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">KDE správca súborov &amp; webový prehliadač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">KDE:s filhanterare och webbläsare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для керування файлами та перегляду сторінок інтернету у KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE File Manager &amp; Web Browserxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE 檔案管理員與網頁瀏覽器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Konqueror is KDE's Webbrowser and swiss-army-knife for any kind of file-management and file previewing.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Konqueror és el navegador web del KDE i una autèntica navalla suïssa per a qualsevol tipus de gestió de fitxers i vista prèvia de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Konqueror is KDE sien Nettkieker un dat swiezer Offiziersmetz för all Problemen bi de Dateipleeg un för Vöransichten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Konqueror is de webbrowser van KDE en Zwitsers mes voor elk soort van bestandsbeheer en bekijken van bestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Konqueror jest przeglądarką sieciową KDE i szwajcarskim scyzorykiem we wszystkich działaniach związanych z zarządzaniem i podglądem plików.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Konqueror är KDE:s webbläsare och Schweiziska armékniv för alla sorters hantering och förhandsgranskning av filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Konqueror — програма для перегляду інтернету у KDE та універсальна програма для керування та попереднього перегляду файлів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKonqueror is KDE's Webbrowser and swiss-army-knife for any kind of file-management and file previewing.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Konqueror 是 KDE 的網頁瀏覽器，以及檔案管理與預覽的好工具。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Webbrowsing using KHTML or KDEWebKit as rendering engines</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Navegació web usant KHTML o KDEWebKit com a motors de renderització</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Nettkieken mit KHTML oder KDEWebKit as Dorstellkarns</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Webbrowsing met KHTML of KDEWebKit als engines voor weergave</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przeglądanie sieci przy użyciu KHTML lub KDEWebKit jako silniki wyświetlania</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Prehliadanie webu pomocou renderovacích enginov KHTML alebo KDEWebKit</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Webbläsning med KHTML eller KDEWebKit som återgivningsgränssnitt</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">перегляд сторінок інтернету за допомогою рушіїв обробки і показу даних KHTML та KDEWebKit;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxWebbrowsing using KHTML or KDEWebKit as rendering enginesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">使用 KHTML 或 KDEWebKit 做成像引擎來瀏覽網頁</li>
      <li>File management using most of Dolphin's features (including version-control, service menus and the basic UI)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Gestió de fitxers usant la major part de les característiques del Dolphin (incloent el control de versions, menús de servei i la interfície d'usuari bàsica)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Dateipleeg mit de mehrsten vun Dolphin sien Funkschonen (ok Verschoonkuntrull, Deenstmenüs un de Brukerböversiet)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bestandsbeheer met gebruik van de meeste functies van Dolphin (inclusief beheer van versies, service-menu's en de basis UI)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie plikami przy wykorzystaniu większości z możliwości Dolphina (włączając w to sterowanie wersją, menu usług i podstawowy układ sterowania)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Filhantering med användning av de flesta funktioner i Dolphin (inklusive versionshantering, tjänstmenyer och det grundläggande användargränssnittet)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">керування файлами за допомогою основних можливостей Dolphin (зокрема можливостей з використання систем керування версіями, службових меню та базового інтерфейсу користувача);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFile management using most of Dolphin's features (including version-control, service menus and the basic UI)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">用大部份 Dolphin 的功能來做檔案管理（包括版本控制、服務選單與基本介面等）</li>
      <li>File management on ftp and sftp servers</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Gestió de fitxers als servidors FTP i SFTP</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Dateipleeg op FTP- un SFTP-Sersvers</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bestandsbeheer op ftp- en sftp-servers</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie plikami na serwerach ftp i sftp</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Správa súborov na ftp a sftp serveroch</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Filhantering på FTP- och SFTP-servrar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">керування файлами на серверах ftp та sftp;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFile management on ftp and sftp serversxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在 ftp 與 sftp 伺服器的檔案管理</li>
      <li>Full featured FTP-client (you can split views to display local and remote folders and previews in the same window)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Un complet client FTP (podeu dividir les vistes per a mostrar les carpetes locals i remotes, així com les vistes prèvies a la mateixa finestra)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">FTP-Client mit all nödig Funkschonen (deelt Ansicht för lokaal un feern Ornern un Vöransichten binnen dat sülve Finster)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">FTP-client met alle functies (u kunt weergaven splitsen om lokale mappen en die op afstand te tonen en voorbeelden in hetzelfde venster)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">W pełni funkcjonalny klient FTP (można dzielić widoki tak, aby wyświetlały lokalne i zdalne katalogi wraz z podglądami w tym samym oknie)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">FTP-klient med fullständiga funktioner (det går att dela vyer för att visa lokala kataloger, fjärrkataloger och förhandsgranskningar i samma fönster)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">повноцінний клієнт FTP (ви можете розділити вікно перегляду на панелі локальної копії та відповідної теки на сервері і переглядати дані з обох тек у одному вікні);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFull featured FTP-client (you can split views to display local and remote folders and previews in the same window)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">完整功能的 FTP 客戶端程式（您可以分割檢視，在同一視窗中同時顯示本地端與遠端的資料夾）</li>
      <li>Embedded applications to preview and edit files (e.g. Okular and KOffice for documents, Gwenview for pictures, KTextEditor for text-files)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Aplicacions incrustades per a previsualitzar i editar fitxers (p. ex., Okular i KOffice pels documents, Gwenview per a les fotografies, KTextEditor pels fitxers de text)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Inbett Programmen för Vöransichten un för't Bewerken vun Dateien (a.B. Okular un KOffice för Dokmenten, Gwenview för Biller un KTextEditor för Textdateien)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ingebedde toepassingen om bestanden te bekijken en te bewerken (bijv. Okular en KOffice voor documenten, Gwenview voor afbeeldingen, KTextEditor voor tekstbestanden)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Osadzone aplikacje do podglądu i edytowania plików (np. Okular i KOffice dla dokumentów, Gwenview dla zdjęć, KTextEditor dla plików tekstowych)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inbäddade program för att förhandsgranska och redigera filer (t.ex. Okular och Koffice för dokument, Gwenview för bilder, Ktexteditor för textfiler)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вбудовування програм для попереднього перегляду та редагування файлів (документи Okular та Calligra, зображення Gwenview, текстові файли KTextEditor)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEmbedded applications to preview and edit files (e.g. Okular and KOffice for documents, Gwenview for pictures, KTextEditor for text-files)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">嵌入式的應用程式，預覽並編輯檔案（如 Okular 與 KOffice 預覽文件，Gwenview 預覽圖片，KTextEditor 編輯文字檔等）</li>
      <li>Different kinds of plugins: Service-menus, KParts (embedded applications), KIO (accessing files using special protocols like http or ftp) and KPart-plugins (like AdBlocker...)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Diferents tipus de connectors: menús de servei, les KPart (aplicacions incrustades), KIO (accés a fitxers usant protocols especials com HTTP o FTP) i connectors amb KPart (com AdBlocker...)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Verscheden Moduul-Oorden: Deenstmenüs, KParts (inbett Programmen), KIO-In-/Utgaavmodulen (Togriep op Dateien över besünner Protokollen as HTTP oder FTP) un KPart-Modulen (as AdBlocker ...)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verschillende soorten plug-ins: Service-menu's, KParts (ingebedde toepassing), KIO (toegang tot bestanden met speciale protocollen zoals http of ftp) en KPart-plug-ins (zoals AdBlocker...)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Różne rodzaje wtyczek: Menu usług, KParts (osadzone aplikacje), KIO (dostęp do plików przy użyciu protokołów takich jak http czy ftp) oraz wtyczki KPart (takie jak AdBlocker...)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Olika typer av insticksprogram: Tjänstmenyer, KParts (inbäddade program), KIO (åtkomst av filer med särskilda protokoll såsom http och ftp) och KPart-insticksprogram (som reklamblockering ...)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">додатки різних типів: службові меню, модулі KPart (вбудовані програми), KIO (доступ до файлів на основі спеціалізованих протоколів, зокрема http та ftp) та додатки KPart (зокрема додатки блокування реклами).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDifferent kinds of plugins: Service-menus, KParts (embedded applications), KIO (accessing files using special protocols like http or ftp) and KPart-plugins (like AdBlocker...)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">各種外掛程式：服務選單，KParts 部件（嵌入應用程式），KIO（使用特殊協定如 http 或 ftp 來存取檔案）與 KPart 外掛程式（如 AdBlocker 等等）</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.konqueror.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=konqueror</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/applications/konqueror/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/konqueror.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>konqueror</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
